Let's get started.
First, let me introduce myself.
I am Sherry from Marvelous Designer.
I am responsible for maintaining our social media platforms,
and providing technical support and training in China.
If you have any questions during the learning process,
you can send me a message anytime.
I will answer your questions in real time,
and I will answer your questions in real time after we finish this live stream.
There are also some other questions during the learning process.
The QR code on the bottom left corner can be copied,
and you can leave a message or send a email.
What about private WeChat?
I don't have a private WeChat.
I never use WeChat.
OK.
Let's get started.
First, when we make Marvelous Designer,
we need to import a virtual model.
When we import a virtual model,
remember to click on the option to automatically add an arrangement.
This will make it easier for us to make arrangements for the costume later.
After I import this virtual model,
I will import the default costume in our system.
You can see that the size is not matching.
It's OK.
Let's arrange it first.
When arranging the version,
I will adjust the properties of our version to arrange the number,
so that it can wrap the virtual model or stay away from the virtual model.
Here you can see,
after I arrange our version,
you can see our sleeve version.
If the auto-arrangement point is not used,
your model may not be human,
or your model is not a T-pose.
For example, the model I imported,
although the arms are open,
it is not a completely flat T-pose.
It is slightly with a little bit of A.
In this case,
the auto-arrangement point function can be used.
This model cannot be shared.
It costs a lot of money to sell.
After we have arranged this version,
you can see that
this version can't be wrapped.
It can only be wrapped around the model's arm.
As you can see,
this model is relatively strong.
So we need to adjust this version later.
Then,
I have widened our sleeve version.
After widening,
you can see that this version has been redesigned.
So we need to rearrange this version.
After the arrangement,
we need to adjust the number of shoulders.
We need to rearrange it again.
Then, we can start the simulation.
After the simulation,
we need to drag the clothing a little bit,
so that it doesn't look so strange.
Now you can see that
because the clothing is tight,
the clothing is always wrapped around the virtual model.
There won't be any wrinkles.
So we need to adjust its shape.
One is,
I widened our clothing a little bit.
This way,
the model can be in a more suitable state
in the chest,
waist,
and other parts.
When you usually
modify the clothing,
I suggest that you can
widen it horizontally first.
Widen it horizontally first,
and then shorten it a little bit.
Instead of
widening it a little bit.
How to do that?
You first widen it entirely,
and then modify it to a more harmonious position.
Then I just felt that
this clothing is a little bit too tight.
So I pulled the front and middle down a little bit.
If it's stuck,
you can refresh it.
It's possible that it's because I've been pausing it all the time.
Okay.
Then after I finished watching it,
I will open a pressure chart
to see if this pressure has a red area.
In the red area,
its pressure is relatively large.
Just to remind you,
this area,
its clothing is a little too tight.
So we have to separate the clothing in this area.
For example,
like this sleeve,
the point here,
pull it wide,
so that it has that amount
that can be worn on the virtual model.
There is no no on the body.
Okay.
Then this sleeve can be seen,
no matter how I drag it,
it has a kind of
like when we usually wear clothes,
it will be stuck here in the sleeve.
The reason for this
is because of its sleeve.
You can see that the model's arm is relatively thick.
If the sleeve is not long enough,
it will cause such a problem.
So I'm going to think about how to deal with this problem.
I looked at it first.
I hadn't found this problem before.
I looked at the pressure map,
and I found that the sleeve was too tight here.
So I will modify it again.
It will look a little better.
Then I found that its shoulder line is forward.
So I moved some of its shoulder line points
and the point in front
in order to match our virtual model.
Then I looked at its collar.
There is a red area here.
I think it doesn't matter.
The collar doesn't care about it here.
Then I looked at its back.
Because this model has a wider back,
and then it suddenly becomes very thin here to the waist.
So we have to adjust its back.
Then I turned on the semi-transparent clothing.
The main function of this function is
that we can check the volume of this clothing.
For example,
the clothing that we are wearing now,
the half of its volume is very large.
You can see that it almost does not cover our virtual model.
So in order to create a more integrated effect,
we can modify it.
And why did I adjust the position of the sleeve here?
It's because I looked at the position of the sleeve of this clothing before.
I think it's a little too close to the arm.
So I made a change to the curve of this sleeve.
Then you can see that
because I changed the curve of the sleeve,
it has a overlap with the large body part.
You can see that there is a small moon-shaped part here.
This part is
if you put this model's clothes on her body now,
if you don't modify its curve,
there will be a volume here.
Once this volume comes out,
there will be a fold.
Yes, I am the most miserable official.
Then we are going to modify the curve of this clothes.
Let it match the curve of this sleeve.
After completion,
we will open the simulation.
You can see that the sleeve here is suddenly much smoother.
After that,
we need to make its length on the side equal.
So let's adjust its length on the side.
Then I see this shoulder line here.
There is some red curve here.
So I pull it forward a little bit.
And the curve of the sleeves
is as smooth as possible.
Don't have a rough feeling.
Yes, if you don't turn on semi-transparent,
you can't see the overlap part.
Because what you see are all white panels.
You may not be able to match them well.
OK.
Let's take a look.
Then I adjust it like this.
Let's take a look at the position of the clothes.
Then I feel that this model has a big belly.
And its back.
I was thinking,
what kind of model is this?
Its upper back can be so wide,
and its waist is so thin.
And then in the back here,
I made it a little bit.
So that it can be close to the curve of our model.
I remember that the back of this model is more curved.
So I also adjusted the curve of this model
to match its back.
Yes.
Everyone is so polite.
OK.
Turn around a little bit.
Sometimes my turning around is actually meaningless.
Just drag it to see.
OK.
Then I can continue.
In order to let this outfit
wear other outfits outside,
I will give it an increase in shrinkage first.
If you often watch my live broadcast,
you should know that
the shrinkage is often used when making clothes.
Especially when dealing with multi-layered clothes.
Just like you are wearing a very tight one inside.
For example,
well,
if you wear a long-sleeved shirt and pants,
you wear it very tight.
Then it will be more convenient for you to wear a sweater outside.
If your sweaters and pants are all loose and wide,
it is not easy to wear a sweater outside.
So here I added a shrinkage to it.
The tail shrinkage is reduced to 80.
It becomes tight again.
Later, we can return it to 100.
Let it become an original costume.
OK.
After completion, freeze it.
Freeze means that
the 3D window will no longer be simulated
or modify its shape.
Then I will use a 3D measuring tool
to measure the waist of this model
or the width of its clothing.
Then it will be more convenient
to make a belt for it.
Then I made a belt for it.
I made a belt with two rectangular panels.
That's it.
How to use the name of that point?
The name of the point is a tool.
It refers to the name of the point
that you arranged on this panel.
Basically, you don't have to care about it.
Shift F can call out the point of arrangement.
Just click the corresponding point of arrangement.
The difference between freeze and reverse activation is that
the freeze panel will maintain
the original conflict.
The freeze panel is completely non-modified.
That is to say,
when you reverse activate a panel,
any panel can penetrate it.
But the freeze panel won't work.
The freeze panel is like
you put an ice cube there.
Your fabric will not pass through it.
Then I will continue to make this belt.
Here I increase its friction coefficient.
When the friction coefficient increases,
the friction of your fabric will be very large.
So it won't fall off easily.
It's not easy to have a relative slide.
After my belt is almost finished,
I will use the false sewing needle tool
to sew this belt
to the top of our clothes inside.
This can prevent it from slipping.
That is to say,
when you do it,
you will sometimes think
why this belt always falls down.
The reason is that
your belt may be tight.
It will find a suitable position by itself.
So sometimes your waist may be
thinner than your legs.
This panel slides down by itself.
So you can use the false sewing needle tool
to fix it.
There is a loop.
Yes,
if you reverse activate it,
there will be a seam line.
Next,
I will insert a pair of pants.
Then,
I will make a cut
by using the internal thread pin.
The internal thread pin
will keep the curve of the line
you choose.
So it will be more convenient
to make a cut.
Then,
I looked at it and thought
its legs are shorter than I thought.
Oh,
I was looking
how to cut it.
Then I remembered
I can cut off the top as well.
Because its length is shorter.
Then I used the 3D drawing tool
to draw a reference line
on this clothing.
Then I used the internal thread pin tool
to draw this line.
In fact,
if you draw it directly,
it doesn't matter.
I just drew a reference line
to make it more accurate.
Then I cut the longer part
of the top.
To adjust it again,
after adjusting its arrangement,
I remember that
I was looking at it
and I was thinking
whether this width is enough.
I kept comparing.
Then I thought,
oh, no,
this pants doesn't seem to fit
its legs here.
Then I kept comparing.
I was looking at
where to put this pants.
Then I continued to cut it.
So in fact,
this model
is much shorter than I thought.
A lot, a lot.
When I think
this position is about right,
I started to simulate it.
Then I adjusted its position a little bit.
In addition,
I think this pants
is...
I think
clowns usually like
to wear lantern pants.
So I will
make a modification
to its
pattern.
I first
adjusted the length
of its side
a little bit.
Then,
I optimized the curve point.
Because sometimes,
this...
I am a little bit forced.
If there are too many curve points,
I will feel uncomfortable.
So I will
optimize the curve point.
This pants
is more integrated now.
I want the effect of
the lantern pants.
So I widened it
on the side.
At this time,
you can see
if you directly put
a very long pattern,
because you see
I have to sew
two very long
patterns on one belt.
There is a wrinkle
at the seam
here.
So you just
want to have...
Yes,
this is a video
while playing
and explaining.
Because I
originally recorded
this video
may take
a few days.
Because I have to
think about how to make
this dress.
In addition,
I have to
add some
content.
Then I look at
its side,
it is a little bit
this length
is a little bit
not right.
Then I will
refer to this
3D dress effect
while
lengthening
these lines.
Then its
curve at the bottom
I don't think
it is very satisfied.
I will continue
to adjust
its curve.
Duan Wu Jie
eat zongzi
no
eat salty
or sweet
What am I doing
here?
I want to
shrink it
and see how to make
its pumpkin pants.
I will broadcast
until 9 o'clock.
9 o'clock
or so.
After it
shrinks,
I remember
something again.
Pumpkin pants
seem to be
puffy on the top
and tight
on the bottom.
So I use the measurement
sheet tool
to adjust
its position
a little bit.
Is it
sour?
Don't
you?
Then you can see
that
this measurement
tool
can directly
cut off
our clothes.
So
what are the benefits
of this function?
Sometimes
you may
have to
cut off
your clothes
along
a certain
horizontal line
or an oblique
position.
You can
cut off
your clothes
by using
a round
board
like this.
You don't
have to
draw
it manually.
Yes,
you can
see it
at B station.
I like
to eat
salty food
but
I also
eat
sweet food.
I don't
steam it.
Then
I cut
the bottom
at the end
because
I thought
it was
too long.
I didn't
use
a
round
board.
Why?
You can see
that
this
one
actually
looks
like
a pumpkin
with
a round
board.
But
if you
add
many round
boards
because
your
grid
hasn
not
been
made
I made
a
T-shape
for it
and sewed it up.
A
foldable
skirt
with
no
wrong
words.
I know
this
too.
No
wrong
words.
This
is not
a skirt.
This
is a
pumpkin
pants.
It's
not
a skirt.
This
is
something
that
I
can't
wear.
It's
not
as
comfortable
a
skirt.
It's
not
as
comfortable
a
skirt.
It's
not
as
comfortable
a
skirt.
On the pants side, you can see that I used to learn fashion design.
On the pants side, we can see that because there are a lot of this kind of pumpkin pants on the side.
In order to make this model look more unadorned, so I want to make her side have the feeling of a lot of pleats.
So I will give her side to increase a shrinkage.
Let her seam line part have a lot of pleats.
You can add a, not a shrinkage, but a elastic.
Here you can see that I set the elastic ratio to 80.
It's okay, this skin is originally black.
The color was adjusted to black.
These different attributes on the right side, I don't know how to use them.
In my last live broadcast, I talked about those about fabric.
If you are referring to this attribute editor,
Usually in some live broadcasts, they are more comprehensive.
You can take a look at our live broadcast.
Or if you have any specific questions, you can ask me directly or send an email.
After this is done, I want to add two flower edges.
Usually, the clown will wear clothes with lotus leaves on the outside.
So I made a round shape for her.
There must be some children who ask, why do you want to draw a round shape?
Can't you draw a square shape?
No, you can't.
You have to draw a circle.
Why?
Because now it is a circle.
When you sew a circle to a side,
It can be folded here in the seam line.
But it will be folded in the outer circle.
Here I drew some internal lines directly to fold it up.
Originally, I wanted it to have the effect of a fan fold.
But I don't think it looks very good.
So I finally added a fan fold in the collar.
So we'll talk about how to fold it later.
I'm just testing the effect here.
You can see that you just need a few tools.
Including our inner line according to the curve.
There are also folding and folding tools.
You can quickly complete this kind of fan fold.
Why don't I keep the fan fold for this side?
Because I think the added fan fold is more and more like a kind of Marcy's clown.
I think it's okay.
I'll keep it for him in the end.
This plain lotus leaf side.
How to turn out.
There is a loop, there is a loop.
How to turn out the clothing model into four sides.
There is a square grid on the right.
Or you can just rematch it.
You can rematch it directly on our software.
After the sewing is complete.
You can see this lotus leaf side.
The difference between this lotus leaf side and the one above is that
It won't fold in the position of the sewing.
It's more like the kind of girl's favorite.
It's a cute sleeve.
Not the kind of.
It's not the kind of.
Well, it's a dead-end embroidery.
Okay.
And then I'm going to use the clasp layer tool.
I clipped a layer of it for him.
Under the flower edge of the original.
Clip layer tool.
It has one advantage.
The version you clipped out.
You can directly maintain the original version of the form.
And then.
They will automatically generate a sewing line between them.
I deleted that sewing line on the live broadcast.
Re-created it.
Then I looked at it and I think it works well.
Just clipped the other half.
Maybe the symmetrical version.
Okay.
When I finished this flower edge.
I suddenly thought about it.
It's like that kind of clown.
He usually has this pumpkin pants.
There's always that kind of bag out there.
A lot of people have a lot of clothes.
There are many structures, so I will gradually tell you the reasons for these special structures in the process.
And then I'm the same, I still put a layer of cloning here.
Sometimes the cloning layer has a more convenient reason,
because the version you cloned will be on top of the original version,
which can help you save a lot of time.
And then after I've created these internal lines,
it's very difficult to have a ghost, so you might want to watch more videos,
or to learn more about some version knowledge,
so that it's easier to grasp.
After drawing these strips, of course you can also draw the strips manually,
but I'm too lazy, I don't want to create the sewing line.
And then after I've completed the side lines,
the four sewing lines,
I found that it's a little unstable sometimes.
Once you see that it's unstable,
you can quickly re-model it.
For example, when I saw the pants over there,
the Neelof's foot came out a little bit,
so I re-modeled it.
I'm sure some of you noticed that I added the yellow part here.
This part is called the lining strip.
This lining strip can help your belt,
or other things like sleeves,
to maintain the original shape.
Lining strip is a professional fashion term.
You will definitely think that it sounds very painful.
As long as you imagine it,
it is a thing that can maintain the original shape of the object.
So after you add a circle of lining strips to the belt,
it will maintain the original rectangular shape,
so it's not easy to stretch it.
This belt will not be able to deform easily.
To learn how to make clothes,
there are many things on it.
Pinterest,
and some of the clothes that you can wear.
Or you can watch the live broadcast of CLO.
It's another clothing software live broadcast in our company.
After I finished it,
I started making his sleeves.
Actually, the idea of making sleeves and pants
is almost the same.
Little crab,
little crab, you're here.
First of all,
let's expand the lining strip first.
This sleeve.
You can see that after the lining strip is expanded,
there is no sewing line on both sides.
So you have to use the editing sewing line tool
to edit both sides.
Oh, it was watching the live broadcast.
It's watching the live broadcast.
That's great.
Then cut and sew it.
Because a lot of clowns
or more noble people
will have puffy sleeves.
So I'm here
to make some adjustments to his sleeves.
Here I am looking at
where to cut this sleeve.
Yes, this doll is a bit strong.
I was thinking at that time
that I want to make him a kind of
noble who is a bit like a beast.
Then
actually,
during the drawing process,
I didn't think about it.
Am I doing a clown?
Or do that kind of
a little bloody,
crazy,
crazy kind of noble.
I did it while I was doing it.
You can see it here.
Because I widened the sleeves,
so he formed
those wrinkles.
Then there is a green line here.
Can you see it?
This green line is a flexible line.
Because if you don't add flexibility,
the sleeves will be opened here.
Yes, it's just several times.
Then I will adjust
this sleeve plate.
You can see that if you put it,
you feel that the amount is not enough,
you just change the point
to make it more.
Then I reduced its particle diameter.
When you reduce the particle diameter,
the distance between the points and the points
in the grid becomes shorter.
Your grid number has changed.
So these wrinkles,
its formation will be more detailed.
There was a loop before.
Our official platform has it.
There is a loop above the station.
It's just that the name may not be called
Marvelous Designer Study Day.
So you can search it.
Here I think this sleeve is not enough to throw.
So I'm thinking about how much pressure to add to it.
You can see that
when you increase the pressure on the sleeve,
it feels like it's full.
Using the method of increasing the pressure
can make your board
have a kind of bumping effect.
Of course,
I think I made it a little too big
when I adjusted it before.
I'll adjust it later.
And then I'll fix it.
The effect of this side sleeve.
Add it and it's frozen.
The number of them is frozen.
One is to reduce
the memory that they stand
to make your computer run faster.
Another one is that the freezing
can maintain its original state.
When you adjust it well,
you don't have to turn on the freezing.
Just freeze the board.
And then I sewed a long strip on it.
Let it be a river side.
It also reduces its strength.
And then when I sit here,
I really feel like a woman.
You see,
like me,
if it is a rectangular board,
it will form such a fold.
From here,
there are folds.
But if you are this round,
arc-shaped board,
because the length of your seam is the same,
it won't fold here.
One is the river side.
There is another one.
It is the side of our umbrella skirt.
Then I will start to make it a vest.
Remove the image.
Okay.
Do you have any problems
in the process of using it?
Since there are so few children
who ask questions.
Here you can see
how to use it.
In order to prevent the clothes
and the inner layer from having a conflict,
I added a layer to it.
It allows the board
to automatically come out
from the inside.
There is also a method
that you may not know
normally.
Okay.
There is also a method
that you may not know normally.
You can turn the shrinkage of the board
into more than 100.
Make this clothes
into bigger clothes.
It will naturally
fit outside the model easily.
When it is simulated
to be stable outside,
you can reduce the shrinkage.
Look,
it can now be
worn outside very conveniently.
There is still no group at the moment.
We have a group of offline activities.
But this year,
because of the pandemic,
there are no offline activities.
So,
the group is not very useful.
Mainly because
I am afraid that there are too many problems.
I can't answer them.
Everyone,
please leave a message.
I go online every day
to collect a wave of leeks
to take a look
to see if there are any children
who leave a message.
Then I will reply below.
Another one is
the mailbox.
It is more convenient
to manage it.
This is also the same.
I am thinking about
how long
the clip
is.
I have been trying it all the time.
How long is more suitable.
I know.
Yes.
You can send me an email.
I received an email.
You can best
put the project file
or you can record it.
You can record it.
Yes.
You can record a video
to tell me
what kind of problem you
have.
It's easier for me
to answer.
Ray,
I got your email today.
I have replied.
But many times
we can't see the project files
and then I added
a dot
to the clip
and pulled it down
to the same shape
that we usually have
on the clip.
Next, expand the outline of the board, and you can see that the face of the board has been extended, so you can add some buttons on it, because its original size is just right.
Now there is a function in our new version, you can add our buttons directly along the outline of the board.
Select the button tool, and then right-click on the outline of the board, and there is a button on the outline of the board, and then you can align it, and then you can add them directly together, and the button will be attached.
It doesn't matter.
Okay.
After this triangle, it looks more like our clown, or I actually didn't think about it at this time.
Am I a clown or a nobleman?
Then adjust some adjustments to this button.
Adjust its thickness and width.
Next, untangle it.
In fact, you didn't pay attention to it.
I already added a contract line to the bottom of this skirt.
Then it's still the same.
I think this vest is not enough to be attached, so I cut off a piece of the side panel.
It's not Milofo.
I haven't put Milofo's big bead on it yet.
Another one is, for example, like this vest, its length on the side is all aligned.
So you must remember to align it.
And then you can see it here.
It's very obvious here.
When everyone is doing it, they may not pay attention.
You can feel it clearly from here.
Most people wear horseshoes that are relatively loose.
It's not like this.
There will be one more piece of it.
So you can fix the inner line first, and then cut this piece of the board.
Otherwise, most horseshoes will look a little weird.
Although it is now getting more and more like women's clothes.
It's not like women's clothes anymore.
No.
In the past, I feel that a little bit earlier,
Eastern, no, Eastern Europe, other nobles in Europe,
they all like to wear it like this.
The beasts in Beauty and the Beast like to wear it like this.
Then I adjusted its buckle a little bit.
I adjusted the position of this buckle because I thought that I would need to do the flower border collar later.
This might block this buckle.
So I went back to adjust it.
Then I made a lotus leaf border for it.
It's the same.
I really like lotus leaf border.
So I added a lot of lotus leaf border and pung pung to the whole model.
Yes, it's automatic.
The cologne layer sewing line is automatic.
So you can tell me what you think of MD or the needs of function development.
Tell me what you think of MD or the needs of function development.
I created an OBJ.
The kids will ask me,
Why do we have a model?
Why?
Why do an OBJ?
If there are gaps,
you can adjust its conflict thickness.
Not a problem with this gap.
Back to the previous topic, when you import OBJ files, you can transform two models with the same number of faces into one.
For example, if you have an OBJ file with an A-Post, you can change it to a T-Post.
I have a model with a T-Post, and I import an A-Post.
When you import it, you can choose to read M of Target, and it will make a change.
It will make a change in the position.
I accidentally accelerated it.
Okay.
Then I will still reduce its particle diameter.
Kids, you might be thinking, why should I reduce its particle diameter?
It's like this.
Um.
If the number of faces of a whole panel is relatively low, and the number of faces is relatively small,
and the number of faces of the clothes in it is particularly large, it is sometimes unstable.
Therefore, if the condition of the outer layer of the clothing is allowed, you can reduce its particle diameter appropriately,
and make the number of faces of its grid larger.
It's not easy and unstable.
Of course, you can maintain the original shape.
It's just that I will reduce the particle diameter of the outer layer because I'm used to it.
Yes.
It's for kids.
Um.
There is no seal on the curtain layer.
You think there is a seal because of this.
The curtain layer automatically comes out of the curtain.
Its sewing line is Turned.
The sewing line of Turned is PinFeng.
It's not PinFeng.
It's DieFeng.
DieFeng is, for example, you have two pieces of paper.
Oops.
Wow.
Oh, my God.
It automatically retreats to the back.
There's an accident.
It scared me.
For example, there are two pieces of paper here.
You fold it.
This is called folding.
Fold it up.
It's called folding.
If you fold it, it will automatically distinguish that there is a gap in the middle.
So there will be a gap.
You can change it to Custom Angle.
That's good.
That's the sewing line.
You use the editing sewing line tool to click on the sewing line.
Wait a minute.
Let me show you.
Use the editing sewing line tool to select the sewing line.
The curtain layer.
The general sewing line is Custom Angle.
The curtain layer is Turned.
Turned.
You can see that there are two pieces of paper stacked together.
It will have a seam.
It's where the seam is.
The rest of the paper will go inside.
reads the paper
Is a texture.
Like this.
I lowered the gain.
I also try to make the air wall between the board and the board louder.
The space between the board.
It's a little below.
Remember that when you make clothes,
if you are stable,
Make sure to change the layer,
Go back,
And then I'm out,
Fight you and then you run around.
Then you go back to the inner layer of the clothes and change it back
So you can see that the clothes inside are getting bigger and bigger
How to change it?
Click the arrow below to change it
Remember to change the layer after you model it
Because I often forget to change the layer
And then my clothes that should be outside suddenly go inside
I think I want to make a collar for this model
It's also a collar that clowns like to wear
How to make it not to have a gap?
You can reduce the thickness of the layer to 0
I will quickly jump over here
Because this is also the same operation as before
Just add a circle
Just sew it up
Here I give this fabric
Because of this round of the tail of the clowns
Its fabric is relatively hard
So here I chose Eau de Gaulle
As the fabric of our collar this time
Eau de Gaulle is the kind of hard sand
You can feel that this collar is flying up little by little
It's because I changed it from ordinary default fabric to Eau de Gaulle fabric now
I will just use this kind of fabric
You can demonstrate it
Wait a minute
What you are saying is
Say there is a panel here
And then the outer part of the dragon
Do you think there is a gap?
Generally speaking, just simulate it
Just simulate it and there will be no gap
If you still feel that there is a gap here and you are not happy with it,
you can change it to a custom angle.
My hand is shaking, I'm afraid I can't move up here.
You see, if you change it to a custom angle, you can move up.
Do you understand, kids?
Change the model's pose.
Does its arrangement not follow the changes?
The arrangement will not follow the model's changes.
If you want the arrangement,
we recommend that when you are wearing clothes,
the model is always T-pose,
that is, the two arms are slightly open,
not slightly, but very open.
Wear it well, then your clothes are almost the same.
After you wear it, you can change its posture.
In addition, if you wear it wrong,
one is the shrink, and the other is the layer.
The layer is really convenient.
Then you can sew the board together.
Wow, time flies so fast.
It's already 8.3g now.
Yes, I used 9.5g.
Then the outer board,
sometimes it has a conflict with the inner board.
Just harden it.
This is more convenient.
When you harden a board,
it is usually not easy for some unstable conditions to occur.
It can be opened relatively quickly.
Then you undo the hardening,
and it can be arranged.
That's it.
It's okay.
Then here,
because I'm using Ogan Shama,
it's too flat now.
I'm not satisfied.
I'm not happy.
I think,
oh, I don't want you to be so flat.
You can be flat,
but don't be so strong.
Then I changed the original fabric back to it.
You can see,
I already have 10 fabrics on the right.
Because I've been adjusting the effect of these fabrics.
OK.
After that,
I'm painting.
I'm painting the little ugly.
It's a little ugly.
There will be that kind of triangle-shaped board outside.
After painting,
I'm going to sew it to our inner circle.
It's on the edge of this circle.
There must be children who say,
why can't I sew inside?
I have to sew on the edge of this river.
It's on the edge of this river.
Well,
I suggest that when you usually sew the version,
you don't sew it in layers.
That is,
you don't want the outer layer
and the inner layer to be sewn together.
Because this sewing line
is piled up in one place.
It's easy to be unstable.
So,
for example,
your first layer of clothes,
you sew it together with the second layer.
Then the second layer
you sew it together with the third layer.
Don't sew it in layers.
Then in order to make this triangle-shaped board stand up,
I applied leather fabric to it.
The leather fabric,
because of its bending strength,
it is easier to stand up.
Like this,
I will use the fixing needle tool
to adjust it.
When I apply the fixing needle tool,
I can see that
I can adjust the angle of the triangle board.
Now,
does it look a little bit like a clown?
At this time,
I have made a new decision
to make it a clown.
What is this question?
If it's a card,
please refresh it.
Wait a minute,
refresh it.
OK.
Then,
I think it's not long enough.
So I made it longer.
But because the position of the fixing needle
has not changed,
so after you make the board longer,
if you adjust this board,
the position of the fixing needle will not change.
So,
when you are changing the board,
you must pay attention.
When there is a fixing needle on the board,
it is best not to change the length of the board.
Because it will affect the shape of the simulation afterwards.
Of course,
if you are more confident,
you feel that it doesn't matter,
then you can not delete it.
OK.
Then I made a few balls.
Because in general,
the outside of this triangle dress of the clown,
there is a ball hanging on it.
After I put the ball in here,
I put it on our board with the glue tool.
Then you can adjust its weight on the right.
You can see that this weight will work on the board.
It will bring this board down.
Then when I put it on,
you can see it very quickly.
This little ball will take this board away.
This board will not be lonely there.
It looks hard.
Then I will paste this ball one by one.
How to do this?
You just pour an OBJ in.
When you pour it in,
you must remember to select the add as a negative key.
Then you can click on it.
You click on this little ball.
It will have a glue tool.
You stick it on the board you want to put on.
Then adjust its weight.
It will work on this costume.
There is a loop.
The glue tool is in the upper right corner.
Wait a minute.
This tool is the glue tool.
See this?
This is the glue tool.
You click on the little ball.
There will be a glue tool here.
Then you click on the glue tool again.
Just click on the board.
It doesn't matter if there is a loop.
We have an official loop.
Don't worry.
Then add the little ball one by one.
In fact, I even turned over the car.
Because when I add the little ball,
did it stick?
Then I didn't care about it.
9.0 has this function.
This function has been around for a long time.
Stick the little ball.
It's MD8.
There is one that can adjust its weight.
Of course, at that time,
little crab,
don't you know MD?
We also held an offline meeting.
At that time,
it was also the new function I introduced.
You see, there is a built-in one.
At that time,
when I first made it,
my colleagues said,
oh,
this,
the more you look at it,
the more you look like Milo.
It doesn't look like a clown at all.
After I added this,
everyone said,
well,
it looks so similar.
It looks so similar.
Next,
I made him a little hat.
First of all,
I made him a hat top.
Then I felt that
this top seems to be a little big.
Then I put it on.
I adjusted its size.
Then I can use this fake-blood-stained tool
to first fix the position of the base plate of this hat.
In order to prevent this hat from changing,
I first used leather fabric for it.
Leather fabric,
in general,
is,
I changed the fold angle to 270
You can see that when you simulate
this side is straight
So you can adjust the fold angle
to make this board stand up
Then I was thinking
What kind of dream am I going to make for him?
Then I was jumping little by little
I was thinking
What kind of hat does this clown usually wear?
I thought for a long time
Oh, I figured it out
It seems that they usually like to wear hats that are not like this
So I did it alone
In order to speed up the computer operation
I re-activated other versions
Because they have no conflict with hats
Then I decided to numb myself first
Give this hat its neck
Use it to
Make the bag on the face first
When can the fabric name be changed?
Because
Let's put it this way
Because the fabric is when you install MD
It is automatically downloaded
It can't follow you
Can't follow your system
So we use English to make it convenient
English material
There may be some optimization in the future
For example, you can directly look at the fabric ball
This is some of the follow-up updates
Sell mutton skewers
Yes, I felt a little wrong at the time
Anyway, I made the edge first
Then I will use this fixed needle tool
To process this edge little by little
This is the model's
On the ground
Anyway, when I did it
I was looking more and more like Millefeu
I think he looks more friendly and friendly
How is MD carving?
It's okay
Just a little bit
Finely carved
It's more convenient to use CB
And there's MD and GOC
It's so convenient
You can go into CB with one click
and carve
Isn't it very convenient?
If you go into CB with four hands
it's also MD carving
Then I deleted
these fixed needles
This is called crossing the bridge
I think it's not very good
I'm not used to it
So I deleted it
When I activated the clothes
I found out one thing
There's still a conflict
So I first
activated the triangle
that will affect
the clothes
You can see
when you activate the triangle
there won't be any conflict
between the pieces
It's like it's gone
Can you see it?
It's dark blue
Then after you stabilize one layer
you activate it
Then use the selection grid tool
to select this grid
the grid on the board
and drag it out
Then you can simulate it
See, it's stabilized now
If you don't
process it layer by layer
then there will be
a lot of conflicts
Oh, I found it here
Oops, I dropped the ball
The mouse can be used to
explain the properties
There will be a material ball
that lets you see
what kind of fabric
this fabric is
In the library,
you can see the preview of this fabric
but it's not that intuitive
It can be changed
It's so good
I'm so touched
I finally have a friend
who uses Gozi
And then
I changed this hat
There must be a careful friend
who found out
It's because
I thought about it
and deleted it
I think
This model is already very big
If you make it
very big
like a little ugly
little ugly yellow
in the digital treasure
I think it's a little weird
So I decided to make it
a shabby
triangle hat
There are some adjustments
down here
Let me take a look at this hat
I think this hat
If it's in the middle
it won't look that good
So I'll adjust it
to the side
Here we have
some adjustments
to this side
You can see
that my
fixed needle has turned
deep red
The reason is because
after I add the fixed needle
there is a button
to attach the fixed needle
to the virtual model
The function of this thing
is very powerful
It is similar to
directly turning the fixed needle
into a fake sewing needle
This way you can
stick some plates directly to your model
If you use the tool
to attach to the virtual model
you can stick it directly
to the virtual model
Then I'll make the
shabby corner of the hat
It's still the same
Just sew the plate
to the plate
Sew the plate
Just sew the hat
to the hat
The strap is fine
Why don't you use the strap function
It's because the strap
is a little big
Of course
be careful
I'm sewing
Sometimes the strap is too big
No, the strap
is a little big
Then sew the plate
to the hat
It's not a hat
It's a round plate
Like this
Okay
Now you can see
that the hat
is gradually
looking like this
When I sewed it
I found that the sewing line
was upside down
So I sewed it again
Then
I was thinking
How can a hat
look like this
Then I changed the fabric
Because the leather fabric
is too hard
The hat can't have the wrinkled effect
when it comes out
I changed it to cotton
It's cotton
Actually
when I simulated it
I found that it was still the same
I thought
I'll pull it by myself
Then I pulled it
Okay
After I pulled it
I was thinking
It seems that the hat
still has a round wrinkled
As a result
I added the wrinkled again
Then to make it easier
to make the wrinkled
I expanded it
and made a ring
to change the movement
and sew it
So actually for half a day
I have to do this
Oh
Right
There should be a small ball on the hat
I said
How come when I finished
I felt something was wrong
Oh
It's because I didn't add the ball
I said
Why do I always feel that this hat
is a little weird
No
I thought this hat looked like a green pepper
Then
It's the same
You add this wrinkled angle
Make it a little stronger
Then adjust it a little
Make it look more wrinkled
No
It's still more like a green pepper
It's green pepper
Get wrinkled
Then adjust the shape
And shape it
I have to adjust the shape
Because I found it
To be kind of bad
Then try to adjust it
To the green pepper
Then I solidified the shape
And remeshing
I will shape it up a little bit
It doesn't have a spicy taste
Okay
Oh, after I adjusted it behind me
Uh, I think this collar seems to be a little bit less
So I choose two ends
There is an internal line created according to the curve
This method can
Create a lot of regular lines very quickly
That's the internal line
Then use this fold-folder to cut the tool
A fold
Oh, he has a lover
Is it very convenient
it is good
It's time for the brothers to brag
Is it completely different from what you saw before
Yes, I just want to make him a very small hat
Is it
It's completely different
Brothers, are you standing up
Uh, when I was showing off
Uh, think about it
Uh, because I think it's a more scary clown
Uh, a scary clown
Actually, I spend more time on this
On the lighting
These choices
Choosing the texture or something like that
It didn't take too long
Um, more
More special is that one is to draw a face for him
Because when I just got that model
I think this model
Um, his texture is a little bit more ordinary
I just want to
I'll draw him a ghost's face
And then like uh
The horror movies I watched when I was a kid
Or something more scary
He always has that kind of
Very strange lighting
Usually this kind of lighting is more like green
It's on the TV screen
It's like a science freak
He likes to use green light
Add a little bit of details
Yes a little bit
Almost
Inflammation plus
These tips
The texture is almost a day
Uh, and then I'm actually on the front
It's a light with a light purple
I don't know if you can see it
Anyway, it's in this
This position
I hit some light purple light
And then I have a green light here
And then here
Yes, I also specially went to watch the movie
And then I hit a red light here
Uh, everyone who has seen my rendering pictures
My little friend will definitely find
I, I like to play
Just one side of a color light
Uh, I actually added a base light
I added a very weak very weak light on the top of this side
Because it sounds pretty funny
I found that after adding a brighter light
This little ugly turned back to Milleford
Then I turned that base light back
There is one more
When I choose these textures
Uh, take a look
I should have opened it in MD
At that time I was in MD
The effect is like this
Yes, I was in MD
The effect is that there is a little transparent here
Then these are all
I use our one texture
I added texture directly in MD
After adding texture
After looking at a general effect
To show
Here I used the texture of swan fur
But MD's swan fur
Can be poured into other 3D software
Let me remind everyone first
So when the time comes, don't ask me
Why did you pour out these textures?
Because I directly used
Another software in our company
Then here these balls
I used some fur textures
Actually there is nothing behind
The main time is spent on
Blending
And some adjustment of this light position
Uh, and this texture choice
I took a little time to choose this texture
Because I
I am not very good at controlling this color
That is, I used to
I usually go with these colors
What to spend more time
What is your problem with MD?
There are some problems
And some suggestions
Can be proposed now
Because now
The part I am talking about
Is almost over
Oh, let me drink some water
Wow, it's really hot here today
Can't
This feather ball material
I directly
Uh
Is in another
In another software
With Vray
I'm using Vray
Is it okay to have a picture?
What do you mean?
Do you mean text?
I have pictures in the text
For beginners
You can see more of our basic teaching videos
Start with
Simple clothes
But look at me
This dress is actually not very difficult
Ah, stickers
Oh, stickers can be
Stickers can be poured out
Is the special material is not good
Because each rendering has its own material
These texture stickers can be poured out
Found stickers can also be
You can have a picture
Stainless steel
Stainless steel is used on one side alone
It's
Stainless steel
You usually add it to the inner line
Or on the outline side of the board
You can just use one side
Because actually you use both sides
And
It's the same effect
Stainless steel
It's equivalent to adding a rubber band
It's actually rubber band
Stainless steel
刚安装MD的时候出现了点击3D面板什么样?
是...嗯...不很...就是...就是点不出来?还是什么?
今天感觉不是很热闹,是不是因为大家都在加班,我哭了?
就会崩溃,你是不是用的AMD显卡,AMD显卡会崩溃?
也不是说一定会崩溃,就是偶发性的。
要不要等一下我换到我的PPT?
嗯,PPT哪个是播放?
啊,不是这个,哦,是的。
大家现在可以有问题可以提问了。
还没有结束,还没有结束,我在的。
感觉今天真的敲后班很少。
感觉今天继续。
还有大家平时有任何的问题和建议,都可以联系模。
还有大家平时有任何的问题和建议,嗯嗯嗯都可以联系我。
嗯嗯。
danxia2 x3
然后是发邮件到我的邮箱都是可以的。
哈 lottery, le Y店...
是总之不管你有什么意见都可以来问我、啊,就是总签的,也就是很完美的。
嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯。
嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯,所以记得对三个秒起!
you can always let me know
Is there really no questions from the viewers?
I remember there was a viewer before
who had some questions
and wanted to answer them in the end
How to use Gozi?
First, you need to go to
the official website
and use the Gozi plugin
After you install the plugin
you can use it
The one I'm using right now